<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<section id="2677">
  <number>0</number>
  <name></name>
  <summary>&lt;img src="@@PLUGINFILE@@/Open%20Your%20Classroom%C2%A0With%20Open%20Educational%20Resources.jpg" alt="" width="400" height="256" role="presentation" class="img-responsive atto_image_button_right"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;Welcome to Open Your Classroom with OER!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This course introduces the wide variety of Open Educational Resources (OER), Creative Commons, and other open licenses. Instructors at all levels of AE will gain an understanding of how to identify and search for materials to use in their teaching practice.
    In addition to learning search strategies, instructors will gain an understanding of how to evaluate OER for appropriate use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Commitment:&lt;/strong&gt; This self-paced course will take approximately 2 hours to complete.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Audience:&lt;/strong&gt; Adult education instructors, trainers, and coordinators.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By the end of the course, participants will be able to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Understand and define Open Educational Resources (OER) and have a foundational understanding of how they can enrich their teaching;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Refine search queries, apply appropriate filters, and determine licensing requirements for Open Educational Resources; and&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Explore, find, review, evaluate, and save materials on the educational repository, OER Commons.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This course is composed of the following:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Course Overview&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Defining Open and Understanding Licensing Options&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Searching for OER and Exploring OER Repositories&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Course Conclusion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the main course page. Each unit of the course includes activities for reflection; and resource lists with links to websites, videos, and other materials to enhance your learning experience. Please note: Items with solid boxes can be self-checked
    to indicate completion; however, all assessments are graded and required for completion. To begin, select “Course Overview” below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: This course was developed under contract with the American Institutes for Research (AIR) with funding from the U.S. Department of Education (ED), Office of Career, Technical, and Adult Education (OCTAE), under &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Contract No. ED-EVP-O-16-F-0001&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;This course has been updated under contract with&amp;nbsp;AIR&amp;nbsp;with funding from the ED, OCTAE, under Contract No.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;i&gt;91990020A-0014/ 91990022F-0346.&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;The&amp;nbsp;content and&amp;nbsp;opinions expressed herein do not necessarily represent the positions or policies of the U.S. Department of Education, and no official endorsement by the U.S. Department of Education should be inferred.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The course may contain resources by a third party outside of the Department of Education. As such, the Department is not responsible for its content, nor can it guarantee it is accessible in accordance with Section 508 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973. If you need access to an accessible version, please reach out to the third-party vendor for assistance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</summary>
  <summaryformat>1</summaryformat>
  <sequence></sequence>
  <visible>1</visible>
  <availabilityjson>{"op":"&amp;","c":[],"showc":[]}</availabilityjson>
  <timemodified>1682356067</timemodified>
</section>